Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Oh,
>> you good. You good?
>> Yeah.
>> Travis.
dude that just like skimmed over. Oh my
god. Oh.
Oh, Jamie, are you all good?
[laughter]
>> Pedal.
I got it on video.
Oh,
>> oh yeah. Jesus.
[laughter]
>> Oh my god.
Okay.
Sweet.
You got it, bro.
Oh, dude.
>> Here.
[__]
Come on, mate. You all right?
>> Ow.
>> Nice.
>> Oh.
>> Oh my god.
>> Oh, going. Oh jeez.
>> Oh.
>> Oh no.
Oh,
ouch.
>> You all right?
>> Pull up. Pull up your
>> Oh,
do a flip.
>> YEAH.
BOY. HEY, BOY.
>> WHOA.
OH.
>> OH.
>> WHOA.
>> And hesitate. Go. Go. Go.
Oh,
heads up.
[laughter]
Oh, buddy.
That sucks.
>> Brakes. BRAKES. BRAKES. BRAKES. BRAKES.
BUDDY. YO, you got to slow down.
[laughter]
Oh my goodness.
>> Yeah, bud.
>> What the heck?
>> Oh god. Rowan,
>> what the hell is that?
>> Rowan, are you okay, dude?
>> I'm totally fine.
Give me something. THAT'S A LITTLE
BETTER. THERE YOU GO. [screaming]
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
YO,
>> you good, bro?
>> Yeah.
>> Pedal, pedal.
>> OH,
>> you okay?
>> Yeah.
Oh god,
that's not how you do it.
[__]
HEY
I Oh no.
Oh.
>> [music]
>> Nobody.
>> Oh. Oh, God. [laughter]
>> You good?
>> Yeah.
You're staying
>> [__]
Oh, my bike. Sorry.
I'll cook speed up.
Holy.
Oh.
Uhoh. Uhoh. Uhoh. Oh, bro. [laughter]
>> Sorry.
[sighs and gasps]
Oh my
Oh boy. [screaming]
>> Oh my god. Oh [laughter] my god.
>> All right, go. Ooh.
[laughter]
>> WOW.
WOOHOO!
Hold on.
Uhoh.
OH,
got to go faster.
Take picture.
Whoa.
>> Oh.
Oh,
>> I'm good.
You all right?
That was too fast. That bike's gone,
bro.
>> Yo.
Oh. Oh.
[laughter]
>> Oh no.
Holy
>> my [screaming]
some speed
Nicole.
>> Are you okay?
>> Jesus.
Guys,
>> oh
>> oh my god.
W. [laughter]
>> Okay.
Oh,
>> pretty wild.
>> You okay?
>> Oh.
Oh, right.
Okay.
What up, my bro?
>> [laughter]
>> Good.
>> Oh [__]
>> Wow.
That was close.
>> Charlie, you all right?
>> Oh my god.
[laughter]
W.
Yeah.
Oh my.
>> Oh.
>> Yeah, it was the hardest.
Yeah.
>> Pedal. Pedal.
Are you okay?
Oh
[__]
Oh,
>> good. You
>> okay?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> He was smiling. Go give it.
>> Oh gosh.
Oh god.
Be the
Whoa.
OH MY GOD.
>> There you go. Money, money, money,
money. Oh, [crying]
what's the [laughter] worst that could
happen?
So here
>> Damn.
>> God damn.
Oh. OH.
>> Oh my.
>> No, you'll be all good.
Never mind.
Holy.
>> You good?
When I smash that thing like
>> Oh, Jesus Christ. Raphael,
>> what are we doing?
>> Oh my god.
>> Yeah.
Go dude. OH
[cheering]
>> WOO. Good job.
Holy
[snorts]
>> dude,
>> are you good?
>> Did you get me hit in the tree?
>> Oh.
Yeah, buddy. Oh, snap.
[laughter]
No, no, no.
Oh. Oh, Todd. Hold on, Todd.
[groaning]
>> [__] We got to go.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Holy.
>> YEAH, BOY. WHOA.
>> SMOOTH. SMOOTH.
>> WHOA.
NO. NO.
>> I'm good.
Yo, that was clean.
Oh god. Oh my god. Eddie.
You
>> all right? Good.
>> You all right?
>> Yeah.
>> See,
get that tight.
Oh my god.
>> Hold on.
Yes.
>> Yes.
>> Yes. Toby.
[screaming]
>> Oh.
Commit. Commit.
Oh. Oh. You good? You good? Your pants
came down.
[laughter]
>> Nice. You got it. You got it.
You got it. Oh.
Oh.
Yeah, baby.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my god.
>> You okay?
>> Oh, he's good.
[snorts]
>> Yo.
Oh,
>> what we want? What we want? Got it.
>> Y.
O.
>> Oh, god.
>> Smash my ow.
>> The one time you film. [laughter]
>> [panting and sighs]
[laughter]
>> You okay?
>> Yeah, I'm good.
OH,
[laughter]
>> come on.
>> You caught it.
>> [music]
>> Whoa. My god.
>> Oh no.
>> Wow.
>> Oh my god. I'm okay. I'm okay.
>> Okay.
>> Mario, take two.
>> Oh [__]
>> You all right? Got
>> him. Full face save me.
>> Full face save. Holy.
>> What is that?
Oh.
[laughter]
Save it.
>> Save it.
>> Oh my god.
Got a great clip of that.